<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MHCapfp</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="mydoctor">My Doctor</string>
    <string name="groupchat">Group Chat</string>
    <string name="treatment">Treatment</string>
    <string name="anxiety">Treatment for anxiety falls into two categories: psychotherapy and medication. Meeting with a therapist or psychologist can help you learn tools to use and strategies to cope with anxiety when it occurs.Medications typically used to treat anxiety include antidepressants and sedatives. They work to balance brain chemistry, prevent episodes of anxiety, and ward off the most severe symptoms of the disorder.</string>
    <string name="depression">Living with depression can be difficult, but treatment can help improve your quality of life. Talk to your healthcare provider about possible options.You may successfully manage symptoms with one form of treatment, or you may find that a combination of treatments works best.It’s common to combine medical treatments and lifestyle therapies, including the following:MedicationsYour healthcare provider may prescribe:antidepressantsantianxietyantipsychotic medicationsEach type of medication that’s used to treat depression has benefits and potential risks.PsychotherapySpeaking with a therapist can help you learn skills to cope with negative feelings. You may also benefit from family or group therapy sessions.Light therapyExposure to doses of white light can help regulate your mood and improve symptoms of depression. Light therapy is commonly used in seasonal affective disorder, which is now called major depressive disorder with seasonal pattern.Alternative therapiesAsk your healthcare provider about acupuncture or meditation. Some herbal supplements are also used to treat depression, like St. John’s wort, SAMe, and fish oil.Talk with your healthcare provider before taking a supplement or combining a supplement with prescription medication because some supplements can react with certain medications. Some supplements may also worsen depression or reduce the effectiveness of medication.ExerciseAim for 30 minutes of physical activity 3 to 5 days a week. Exercise can increase your body’s production of endorphins, which are hormones that improve your mood.</string>
    <string name="insomia">There are both pharmaceutical and nonpharmaceutical treatments for insomnia.Your doctor can talk to you about what treatments might be appropriate. You may need to try a number of different treatments before finding the one that’s most effective for you.The American College of Physicians (ACP) recommends cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) as a first-line treatment for chronic insomnia in adults.Sleep hygiene training may also be recommended. Sometimes, behaviors that interfere with sleep cause insomnia. Sleep hygiene training can help you change some of these disruptive behaviors.Suggested changes may include:avoiding caffeinated beverages near bedtimeavoiding exercise near bedtimeminimizing time spent on your bed when you’re not specifically intending to sleep, such as watching TV or surfing the web on your phoneIf there’s an underlying psychological or medical disorder contributing to your insomnia, getting appropriate treatment for it can alleviate sleep difficulties.</string>
    <string name="phobia">Treatment for phobias can involve therapeutic techniques, medications, or a combination of both.Cognitive behavioral therapyCognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) is the most commonly used therapeutic treatment for phobias. It involves exposure to the source of the fear in a controlled setting. This treatment can decondition people and reduce anxiety.The therapy focuses on identifying and changing negative thoughts, dysfunctional beliefs, and negative reactions to the phobic situation. New CBT techniques use virtual reality technology to expose people to the sources of their phobias safely.MedicationAntidepressants and anti-anxiety medications can help calm emotional and physical reactions to fear. Often, a combination of medication and professional therapy is the most helpful.</string>
    <string name="schriz">Most people with schizophrenia aren’t diagnosed until the second phase, once symptoms worsen and become more obvious.At this point, treatment options include:Medicine. Antipsychotic medications may be able to influence the level of chemicals and neurotransmitters in the brain. This could reduce symptoms. It might also help a person avoid relapses or worsening symptoms.Therapy. A doctor may refer a person with schizophrenia to a psychologist or psychiatrist. These mental health experts can help people learn to work through disordered thought patterns. They can also help recognize signs of a possible relapse.Hospitalization. This emergency treatment is for an individual in immediate danger. Suicidal thoughts or hallucinations may pose a risk to the persons safety, or even to people around them.</string>
    <string name="ocd">Obsessive compulsive disorder (OCD) can be treated. The treatment recommended will depend on how much it\'s affecting your life.The 2 main treatments are: psychological therapy – usually a type of therapy that helps you face your fears and obsessive thoughts without putting them right with compulsions medicine – usually a type of antidepressant medicine that can help by altering the balance of chemicals in your brain.A short course of therapy is usually recommended for relatively mild OCD. If you have more severe OCD, you may need a longer course of therapy and/or medicine.These treatments can be very effective, but its important to be aware that it can take several months before you notice the benefit.</string>
</resources>
